[Music]
hey come on
in yes push and believe you got it so
Mike you're in Boston if you want to get
comfortable and take the jacket off I
like the jacket I'm going for the single
dad look are you a single f no no I just
like portraying the illusion of do you
have a significant other yeah I do yeah
I have a girlfriend where did you guys
meet the internet is that a club yeah
where is that uh desperation. comom um I
need this.org you do poetry yeah I did I
did I'm a recovering Slam Poet 88 years
sober are you going to go back to your
roots for this comedy special I do some
rhyming can you rhyme on the spot I know
when they say comedians like do a joke
for me and they go don't ever make me do
a joke I could do yeah okay so you can
do the Poetry so I'm Mike Lawrence I'm
in this hotel this conversation is
awkward as hell uh I don't know where
it's going and I don't know how it'll go
let's be honest this poem blows
you think this is an awkward interview
it's different no no no no no just it
was I was just going with you're going
with it let me try
yeah hanging out and Boston doing what I
do drinking Dunkin Donuts with the
morning dew get get out of my bed
stretch and do that call my little
mother she won't call me back jump into
the shower scrub my little body stare
into the mirror just like everybody I
said body twice that's a thing you don't
want to do when you're doing a poem like
a hi
cou yes push and believe you got it but
I love that that that started off as a
slam poem but you slowly became more and
more like the lead singer from the
b52s oh I turned into I got me a car
it's as big as a wh like it really
became like Y
what what you know you're talking about
Fred Schneider you know uh I get that
comparison on a I am 10% gay I'm open
about it I went to Bangkok I pushed it
to the Limit anything you want to open
up about uh yeah I I I uh I dated a dude
for 3 weeks in college and dumped him
because he gave me the worst hand job
that I ever got it in my life uh they're
supposed to be good at that right like
that's the reason you're with another
dude cuz he knows how to touch the stuff
uh it was horrible it was like if King
Arthur had had Parkinson's when he
pulled out Excalibur that's how my dick
felt it was painful and I I I was just
like I can't I can't do this like and
the sad thing was this was a
Thanksgiving after he had introduced me
to his family and came came out to him
and said this is the guy that I
love wow I I did it it was not in the
bio I didn't know who I was you know and
so I was like I'll I'll try this this
sounds fun feel like we're connected
we've been too far apart let's single it
and get closer Michael thank you yeah
how's it going I want you to open up and
and say Brody I'm there I'm comfortable
with my gayness I was gay in the same
way that Michael Jordan was a b baseball
player are you a baseball fan maybe
that's something we can connect no no no
I don't like any sports you don't like
sports no do you exercise no are you
depressed yeah do you think exercise
will help your depression no Michael yes
I've been where you're at I've been
depressed I've been on medication I've
been under doctor's
supervision and what they tell me is
exercise is the way to go
will you do that with me right now yeah
let's do it yes we're exercising we're
pushing I'm here with Mike how do you
feel right now Mike oh this is so
uncomfortable you know push through it
the depression is fading where going to
The Love Shack baby oh we're back to
that how dare you call me
Schneider you got it Mike Lawrence
Steven Brody Stevens exercising you got
it see us on Comedy Central very
soon
click like
subscribe click and like it on Facebook
subscribe and it
onbook
subscribe and like it on Facebook you
liked it and like it on Facebook
subscribe
video like it on Facebook